



# **Hoang Bao Vo (Andy)**

**Date of birth:** 19/09/1998 | **Nationality:** Vietnamese | **Gender:** Male |

Phone number: (+49) 15750625876 (Mobile) | Email address:

andy.vo.98vn@gmail.com | LinkedIn: linkedin.com/in/bao-vo-hoang | Github:

https://github.com/andyvo190998 | Portfolio:

https://andyvo190998.github.io/animated-portfolio/

Address: Friedberger 5, 86161, Augsburg, Germany (Home)

# ABOUT ME

I am a self-taught web developer with knowledge of **NextJS**, **ReactJS**, **NodeJS**, **and Python** with 3 years of experience. Although, I do not study computer science but as a young man, I am an enthusiastic, self-motivated, reliable, responsible, hard-working person who can be able to adapt to all challenging situations. I can work well both in a team environment as well as using my own initiative. Please visit my **GitHub** repositories and **portfolio** website to see my work to learn more about me.

## WORK EXPERIENCE

10/12/2019 - 31/12/2020 Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

### **SOLAR ENERGY ENGINEER SOLARBK**

Research and find out new technologies that improve the efficiency of solar modules, receive feedback from clients and find the solution to fix that issue on Solar panels.

01/07/2021 - 01/10/2021 Singapore, Singapore

## **WEB DEVELOPERS FULLERTON HEALTH**

As a part-time full stack web developer, I was responsible for maintaining, debug, add new features for their website by using ReactJS, NodeJS.

01/04/2023 - CURRENT Munich, Germany

# **SOFTWARE DEVELOPER KIUTRA GMBH**

- Creating and maintaining front-end using React|S to run physics low-temperature experiment
- · Handling front-end requests with back-end using Flask, Quart, Websocket
- Creating and maintaining middleware using Python for front-end and back-end communication
- Brainstorming ideas for low-temperature physics measurement with R&D team

## EDUCATION AND TRAINING

01/06/2016 - 01/10/2020 Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam

**BACHELOR'S DEGREE** Ho Chi Minh University Technology and Education

My major is material technology, more specifically, I study about some devices like Transistors, MOSFET, LED, Sensors, TCO,... nanostructure, simulation properties of materials, semiconductors, thin film technology,... deep knowledge of semiconductors and Transistor and General Electronics

Address 1 Vo Van Ngan, Thu Duc, Ho Chi Minh, Viet Nam, 71300, Ho Chi Minh, Vietnam | Website hcmute.edu.vn |

Field of study Physics , Chemistry , Physical sciences not elsewhere classified | Final grade GPA: 7.64/10 |

Thesis Thesis: 9.6/10

## **MASTER OF SCIENCE** University of Augsburg

Continues with the subjects of bachelor's degree, I keep digging deeper into Semiconductor Technology, and gain more knowledge of Semiconductor devices (E.g Transistor, Solar cells,...), understand the way it works and how to create it. Beside of that, I am learning the properties of other materials such as Metals, and polymer composites,...

Address Universitätsstraße 2, Augsburg, 86159, Augsburg, Germany | Website www.uni-augsburg.de |

Field of study Chemistry, Physics | Thesis The properties of Cul thin films prepared by spin coating.

## LANGUAGE SKILLS

Mother tongue(s): **VIETNAMESE** 

Other language(s):

	UNDERSTANDING		SPEAKING		WRITING
	Listening	Reading	Spoken production	Spoken interaction	
ENGLISH	C1	C1	C1	C1	C1
GERMAN	A2	A2	A2	A2	A2

Levels: A1 and A2: Basic user; B1 and B2: Independent user; C1 and C2: Proficient user

### DIGITAL SKILLS

Python | express | React|S | Node|S | git | MySQL | Gi,Bitbucket | typescrypt

## ADDITIONAL INFORMATION

# **HONOURS AND AWARDS**

05/12/2021

**Project Manager – Coursera** Those who earn the Google Project Management Certificate have completed six courses, developed by Google, that include hands-on, practice-based assessments and are designed to prepare them for introductory-level roles in Project Management. They are competent in initiating, planning and running both traditional and agile projects.

Link <a href="https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/specialization/certificate/UW5R4PX9ZCVV">https://www.coursera.org/account/accomplishments/specialization/certificate/UW5R4PX9ZCVV</a>

#### 28/12/2021

**Web developer – Freecodecamp** From this course, i was learning a lot of basic knowledges about javascript and data structure.

**Link** <a href="https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/fcc71b5460b-8133-41f4-94fc-5727c76f5015/javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures">https://www.freecodecamp.org/certification/fcc71b5460b-8133-41f4-94fc-5727c76f5015/javascript-algorithms-and-data-structures</a>

## 26/02/2022

**web developer – Udemy** This course guides me from front end to back end and including data base like MongoDB.

Link https://udemy-certificate.s3.amazonaws.com/pdf/UC-acdd3aa5-ddc5-4778-93b5-c2c5eee59f29.pdf